{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The title of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"Partings.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"Shadow and Flame\". It was released on October 14, 2022.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The title of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"Shadow and Flame\".",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The title of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"Shadow and Flame\".",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The title of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The title of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"Alloy.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The title of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "A Shadow of the Past",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The title of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is called Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The title of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 11
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"The Eye of the Storm.\" It was released on September 1, 2022, and is the seventh episode of the show'",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"The Eye.\" It was released on September 1, 2022.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"The Eye.\" It was released on September 1, 2022.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"The Eye.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"The Eye.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"The Eye of the Storm.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"The Eye.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"The Eye.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"The Eye of the Storm.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "A Shadow of the Past",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is \"A Shadow of What Was Lost\".",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is called \"A Shadow of the Past.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is A Shadow of the Past.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is called \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"The Eye of the Storm.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Shadow and Flame is the title of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is called \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is titled \"Shadow and Flame.\"",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "needle": "The most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power is Shadow and Flame.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the name of the most recent episode of The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power?",
      "frequency": 8
    }
  ]
}